Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
- Box: 119, Folder: 8 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and Westinghouse Motor Salaried Employees' Association Affiliated with Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, Publication (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Supplement I Dated the First Day of May, 1947 Supplement to Agreement Dated the First Day of April, 1947 between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and Associated Welders of Western New York, Inc., Publication (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Personnel Maunal, Publication (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Box: 119, Folder: 9 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Scholarships by Westinghouse, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Strange Peoples of the Little Worlds: a story of the tiny beings that give both life and death, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Eyes for the Little Worlds: How we see into the tiny invisible universes that thrive on everything we see and touch, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Heritage of the Soil: New things we make from farm products, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Today's Ben Franklins: What we know about lightning and why we study it, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Amber and Amperes: What we know of electricity and how we use it, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Books by Westinghouse Authors, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Welcome to Westinghouse, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Graduate Student Training, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: A Statement by Gwilym A. Price before Annual Meeting of the Stockholders, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
    By Gwilym A. Price. April 17, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Worker and the The Works, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Operation Catch-Up: Facts for Bargaining, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Shop Practice of the Westinghouse Electric & Mfc. Co., Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Information for Employees: Westinghouse Electric & Mfg. Co. Electric Works, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Your Sever Keys to Security, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: The Industrial Supervisor: His Characteristics, Duties, Responsibilities and Opportunities, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: The Industrial Supervisor: His Job and His Development, Pamphlet Six-Economics, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Westinghouse War Veterans' Reinstatement Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Westinghouse Attachments, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Physical Capacities Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: A Statement by A. W. Robertson, Chairman Westinghouse Electric Corporation, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
    January 15, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Wekearnyans' Guide to Coming Club Activities: The Clubcaster Vol. 1 No. 24, Publication (Box 119, Folder 9)
    August 5, 1947. Item is in English.
- Box: 119, Folder: 10 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Statistics for Problem Solving and Decision Making, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Tuition Refunds for out-of-hours College Study, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Continued Education for Westinghouse Professional Personnel 1969-1970, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Westinghouse Orientation of New Employees, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Westinghouse Learning Corporation providing tomorrow's educational systems today, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: R&D News Vol. 8, No. 2, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    January-February 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Linguaphone for Languages, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Memo on the Science Talent Search, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    February 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Management Organization, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    February 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Manual of Salary Administration: for the Guidance of Supervisors, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    March 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Merit for Management Salary Increases, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Management Guide: Management Salary Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Management Guide: Management Performance Objectives, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Management Guide: Reassignment of Management and P&A Personnel, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    October 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Management Guide: Management and Professional Personnel Development, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    September 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Westinghouse Insurance Plan/Pension Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: The Foreman's 14 Toughest 'People' Problems, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Westinghouse Personal Investment Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Westinghouse Personal Savings Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Long-Term Disability Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    Revised July 1, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Personal Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Westinghouse Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: DC Circuits AC Circuits: an individualized approach to Electronics by Westinghouse Learning Corporation, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Westinghouse Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Headquarters Employe Handbook, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: a NOW learning success experience, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: A Guide for Safety Observers, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: In-Hospital Idemnity Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    Effective January 1, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: A New Series Health Instructional Programs for Professionals, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Put Well-Trained Welders On-Line Quickly, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Westinghouse Pension Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    Revised August 1, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Design Experiments Course: A VISTEX Service for On-Site Professional Development, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 33: Westinghouse Learning Corporation, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: Open the lid to the TREASURE TUB and make learning come alive!, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 35: Westinghouse Personal Savings Plan, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 36: A Major Breakthrough in Individualized Learning, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 37: Catalog of Courses and Seminars: 1975, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 38: PLAN: An Individualized Learning System, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 39: Special Education '75, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 40: Westinghouse Safety Program and Performance Evaluation Part 4, Section 1, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 41: Inter-Office Correspondence: Summary Plan Description, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
    February 10, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: What's Your Opinion? An Employee Attitude Survey for Employes of the Westinghouse Electric Corporation Power Generation Service Division, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 43: Hourly Job Description, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 44: Salary Position Description, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Item 45: 1966 Safety Report: Westinghouse Electric Corporation, Publication (Box 119, Folder 10)
- Box: 119, Folder: 11 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Management Functions and Policies Course, Publication (Box 119, Folder 11)
- Box: 119, Folder: 12 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Westinghouse Operation Analysis, Publication (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Statistics for Problem Solving and Decision Making: A course on Quantitative methods for management and professional personnel, Publication (Box 119, Folder 12)
- Box: 119, Folder: 13 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Special Recognition Program, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Weyerhaesuser Exercise Club, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: dental Care Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
    Revised January 1, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Program for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
    Revised July 1, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Health Care Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
    Effective July 1, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Reference Handbook for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Management Assemssment of Potential Report, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Corporate Educatio Projects/Activities--September, 1975, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Educational Assistance Plan--Policy, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: State DNR issues tmber supply report, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
    September, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: 25 Years of Progress, Publication (Box 119, Folder 13)
    1929-1954. Item is in English.
- Box: 119, Folder: 14 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your Benefits Summarized at Whirlpool, Publication (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: V.I.P., Publication (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Whirlpool Benefits for you and your family, Publication (Box 119, Folder 14)
- Box: 119, Folder: 15 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 119, Folder 15)
- Box: 119, Folder: 16 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Whitin Machine Works: Whitinsville, Mass., Publication (Box 119, Folder 16)
    January 1, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 119, Folder: 17 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Wholesale Hat & Cap Mfrs. Ass'n Incorporated, Publication (Box 119, Folder 17)
    June 29, 1927. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Wholesaler, Publication (Box 119, Folder 17)
    January 30, 1926. Item is in English.
- Box: 119, Folder: 18 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Working Women: a model program to train women for jobs in non-traditional occupations, Publication (Box 119, Folder 18)
- Box: 119, Folder: 19 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Multiple Management, Publication (Box 119, Folder 19)
- Box: 119, Folder: 20 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Public Affairs Information Service: A Cooperative Clearing House of Public Affairs Information, Publication (Box 119, Folder 20)
- Box: 119, Folder: 21 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Exempt Employee Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Wilson Foods, Publication (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Exempt Employee Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Wilson Foods Corporation, Publication (Box 119, Folder 21)
- Box: 119, Folder: 22 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing Really Works at American Velvet Co., Publication (Box 119, Folder 22)
    By E. H. Helliwell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Partners in Velvet, Publication (Box 119, Folder 22)
    By Clarence A. Wimpfheimer. Item is in English.
- Box: 119, Folder: 23 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Plant Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 119, Folder 23)
    January, 1945. Item is in English.
- Box: 119, Folder: 24 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Training Programs Designed to Meet Nine Objectives, Publication (Box 119, Folder 24)
    By A. H. Nielsen. May 19, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 119, Folder: 25 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Minutes of Harvester Industrial Council, Wisconsin Steel Works, Publication (Box 119, Folder 25)
    January 4-December 6, 1921. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 1 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union-Community Handbook, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Virginia Hart. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Twenty-First Year of Educational Service to Labor, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By John R. Commons. 1925-1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: "The Wisconsin Idea" in Workers Education, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By E. E. Schwarztrauber. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The University of Wisconsin School for Workers: Its First Twenty-Five Years, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Ernest E. Schwarztrauber. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Full Employment, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Walter A. Morton. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor Journalism Workshop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Harold J. Newton. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor Journalism Workshop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Making Education Work for the Union, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Harold J. Gibbons. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Union Service Institute, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    August 7-12 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Unions Attitudes Towards Workers Education, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Larry Rogin. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The University of Wisconsin IRRI Report, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: The University of Wisconsin IRRI Report, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: The University of Wisconsin IRRI Report, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    December 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The University of Wisconsin IRRI Report, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    June 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The University of Wisconsin IRRI Report, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    February 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Industrial Relations Research Institute The University of Wisconsin, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    August 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industrial Relations Research Institute The University of Wisconsin, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    December 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: What's Wrong with Labor Papers?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Sam Sherman. March 1-2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Impending Merger of the A.F.L. and C.I.O., Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Recent Labor Legislation of Interest to Labor, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    By Edwin E. Witte. July 9, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 2 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: National Program for Economic Equality: Presentation to the 1980 Working Women's Conference, Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
    By Beata Welsh. October 11, 1980. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 3 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Women Working in Construction, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Box: 120, Folder: 4 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: WAJE-earner: raises, not roses! Vol. 1, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
    December, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Fact Sheet--Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
    November 15, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Interfaith Project: Getting the Job Done, Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
    By Marci Shatzman. September 28, 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 5 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Women's Century Club Yearbook 1919-1920, Publication (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Box: 120, Folder: 6 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Equal Rights Amendment for Equal Justice Under Law: Joint Resolution, Publication (Box 120, Folder 6)
    October 1978. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 7 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: WIN News Vol. 1, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 7)
    October 1975. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 8 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Personal Adventures in Race Relations, Publication (Box 120, Folder 8)
    By Ether Popel Shaw. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 9 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Shortchanged and Slighted: An Assesment of the Department of Labor's National Response to Women's Employment and Training Needs, Publication (Box 120, Folder 9)
- Box: 120, Folder: 10 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the Woodward & Lothrop Employees' Association, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Organized 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Excerpt from letter of August 23, 1934, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    By P. W. Talbott. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: System No. IV, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: System No. I, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: System No. II, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: System No. III, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Employee Information Card, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Recommendation of Change in Rate, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Applicant acceptance form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Entrance Tests, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Application for Employment with Woodward & Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Entrance Tests, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Wood Lothian, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    January 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Wood Lothian, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    December 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Wood Lothian, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    June 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Performance Review Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Organization Chart of Woodward & Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    December 1, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Performance Review Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Supervisory erformance Review, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Fall 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: 1958 Annual Executive Performance Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: This is Woodward + Lothrop: a handbook for all store members, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Organization Chart: Woodward + Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    March 1, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: 1962 Annual Executive Performance Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Performance Review Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Supervisory Performance Review, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Woodward + Lothrop Organization Chart, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: Supervisory Performance Review, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Spring 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Executive Performance Evaluation, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Work Simplification and Store Members Proposal Plan: Looking for a better way at Woodward + Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    April 1, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Group Annuity Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    July 1, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Welcome! What You Want to Know About Woodward + Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 33: Welcome! What you Want to Know About Woodward + Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: Group Annuity Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Effective July 1, 1944; Amended and Effective July 1, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: What You Will Want to Know, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Revised January 3, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: What You Will Want to Know, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Revised September 1, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: What You Will Want to Know, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Revised September 15, 1931. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: What You Will Want to Know, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Revised October 1926. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Constitution and By-Laws of the Woodward & Lothrop Employees' Association, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 40: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 41: The Retiremnet Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Effective July 1, 1944; Amended and Effect July 1, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: The Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 43: A Report to Store Members on the Opinion Poll, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 44: It's Smart to be Busy at Woodward + Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 45: There is a Retail Career for you at Woodward + Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 46: Woodward & Lothrop News Bulletin, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    October 8, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Supervisor and Administrative Performance Review, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 48: Supervisor and Administrative Performance Review, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 49: Bulletin Boards, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 50: Opinion Poll of Woodward & Lothrop Store Members Conducted by The Attitude Research Section of the Psychology Department of the George Washington University, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 51: Fundamentals of Economics, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 52: Some Principles of Psychology, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 53: Thurstone Employment Tests, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    By L. L. Thurstone. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Semi-Annual Rate Review, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 55: Extracts from the Constitution of the Woddward & Lothrop Employees' Association, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 56: Sales and Rate Report, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 57: Woodward + Lothrop Applicant Decision Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 58: Service Record, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 59: Registration Slip, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 60: Changes in Rate, Cause of Leaving, Etc. Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 61: Registration Slip, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 62: Service Record, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 63: Application for Employment with Woodward & Lothrop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 64: Building the Human Organization, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 65: Military Furlough, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Item 66: Performance Review Form, Publication (Box 120, Folder 10)
    Spring 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 11 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: City of Woonsocket: State of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations, Engineer and Boiler Operator Licensing Act, Publication (Box 120, Folder 11)
    Approved April 24, 1944. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 12 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Trends in Church, Education and Industry Cooperation Vol. 6, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 12)
    February, 1950. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 13 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Workers' Bank News: A Quarterly Publication Vol. 1, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 13)
    January 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Workers' Bank News: A Quareterly Publication Vol. 1, No.4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 13)
    March 1975. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 14 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Union Security: Closed Shop, Maintenance of Membership, Preferential Shop, Union Shop, Publication (Box 120, Folder 14)
- Box: 120, Folder: 15 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: High Wages; the Basis of Recovery, Publication (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: High Wages: the Basis of Recovery, Publication (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: The Pioneer Institute of Labor: An Experiment in Understanding, Publication (Box 120, Folder 15)
- Box: 120, Folder: 16 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Working/Women United Institute Project Statement: Sexual Harassment on the Job, Publication (Box 120, Folder 16)
- Box: 120, Folder: 17 (Box 120, Folder 17)